{
    "subject": "resource/Southwest_Airlines",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Southwest Airlines Co. (NYSE: LUV) is a major U.S. airline and the world's largest low-cost carrier, headquartered in Dallas, Texas. The airline was established in 1967 and adopted its current name in 1971. The airline has nearly 46,000 employees as of December 2014 and operates more than 3,400 flights per day. As of June 5, 2011, it carries the most domestic passengers of any U.S. airline. As of November 2014, Southwest Airlines has scheduled service to 93 destinations in 41 states, Puerto Rico, and abroad.Southwest Airlines has used only Boeing 737s, except for several years in the 1970s and 1980s, when it leased some Boeing 727s from Braniff. As of August 2012, Southwest is the largest operator of the 737 worldwide with over 650 in service, each averaging six flights per day.As an employer, Southwest was ranked #15 in the Glassdoor Employees\u2019 Choice Awards 2015.",
    "human_readable": "Southwest Airlines is a major U.S. airline and the world's largest low-cost carrier, headquartered in Dallas, Texas.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9406743049621582,
            "question": "Is Southwest Airlines the largest low-cost carrier globally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8471955060958862,
            "question": "In which U.S. state is Southwest Airlines headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8120167255401611,
            "question": "Where is Southwest Airlines headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7167006731033325,
            "question": "What type of airline is Southwest Airlines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5764545202255249,
            "question": "What is Southwest Airlines known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5266175270080566,
            "question": "Besides the United States, does Southwest Airlines operate in other countries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5075516104698181,
            "question": "What distinguishes Southwest Airlines from other airlines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48110514879226685,
            "question": "What are some of the destinations served by Southwest Airlines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31090816855430603,
            "question": "Does Southwest Airlines offer international flights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2531008720397949,
            "question": "How would you describe Southwest Airlines' business model?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Southwest Airlines is a major U.S. airline and the world's largest low-cost carrier, headquartered in Dallas, Texas.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4706_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Southwest Airlines offer international flights?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4706_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the destinations served by Southwest Airlines?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4706_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What distinguishes Southwest Airlines from other airlines?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4706_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4706_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4706_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4706_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4706_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4706_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4706_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4706_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4706_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4706_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4706_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple as it can be found in multiple files (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4706/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4706/re-ranker-msmarco/80.txt) that describe Southwest Airlines as a major U.S. airline and the world's largest low-cost carrier, headquartered in Dallas, Texas."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently state that Southwest Airlines is a major American/U.S. airline and the world\u2019s largest low-cost carrier, which is also headquartered in Dallas, Texas. Therefore, the provided statement is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}